Liu Heizi.
What skills.
Old man.
Take them down!
Yes, sir.
Tie these men up.
Keep a close eye on them.
Report to me immediately if there's any problem.
Today, Chai Jiu
disobeyed orders
and shall be punished.
Tie him up as well.
I still have use for him.
The rebellion in the south has been suppressed,
with continuous reports of victory.
General Tong
is getting too much attention.
As long as there is a war,
the General won't be in the capital.
His Majesty
will still rely on you more in the future.
Don't worry, Grand Eunuch.
Water.
Stand up straight and behave.
Speak up if you want water.
Answer honestly
when Commander Chu asks.
Meng Qian.
A native of Bianjing,
living in Anren Ward.
Known as the Tokyo Geography Ghost.
You have a widowed sister-in-law who sells sachets
and a bedridden sister.
My lord,
they don't know anything.
What do you want to know?
Ask me.
Then tell me everything.
If you lie,
I will immediately invite your sister-in-law and sister here.
I will tell you everything.
Why were you at Wuyou City that day?
Who were your companions?
What is this about?
Tell the truth.
I...
Commander.
Lord Zhou You is in Fengsheng Hall.
Please go see him immediately.
I am Chu Sanniang.
Greetings, Lord Zhou.
Commander Chu.
I heard
you led your men on a killing spree in the market today
and made a huge scene.
Is that true?
Reporting to Duke Zhou.
Last night outside Dongjing,
two heralds
were brutally assassinated.
I am worried
that this involves the Emperor's safety on the Lantern Festival.
So I followed the clues
to track down the assassins and rebels.
This is ciphertext.
Your Highness.
The Liangshan rebels
entered Wuyou City to trade.
They must have come for this military defense map.
The rebels want to climb the West Tower of Fanlou.
It is quite interesting.
Then,
this military defense map...
Let's wait and see.
Ridiculous!
Rebellions across the country
have all been defeated by our army,
retreating continuously
and surrendering.
What rebel would dare to come to Dongjing?
Report to Lord Zhou,
I
have indeed found out through investigation
that assassins have sneaked into Dongjing City,
intending to do something unlawful to the Emperor
on the night of the Shangyuan Festival.
This matter concerns the safety of the Emperor,
which is the responsibility of Bingjingwu.
I
dare not neglect it.
You should know that
while the Emperor's safety is naturally important,
his reputation
must also be maintained.
The Shangyuan Festival
is a joyous occasion celebrated by all.
Moreover, envoys from Liao, Jin, and Goryeo
are gathering in Dongjing City.
How could our great Song Dynasty
let these barbarians
make a joke out of us?
Then,
what do you mean, My Lord?
This year on the Shangyuan Festival,
the Emperor is going up Fanlou again.
The rumors of an assassination
are about to spread all over Dongjing.
The Emperor loves to have fun.
Let him be.
Assassins appear from time to time,
but I haven't seen many who can get near the Emperor.
This time the rumor says
they are rebels from the uprisings.
Bingjingwu
has already caused quite a stir.
The hard chore of catching thieves
is mostly a waste of effort.
Since Capital Chief Chu loves to waste her effort,
let her work to her heart's content.
What if
she really catches the thieves?
She can report directly to the Emperor.
Catching thieves is hard.
But once the thieves are caught,
snatching them away to claim credit
is a piece of cake, isn't it?
Commander Chu,
right now,
factions inside and outside the court are surging.
Everyone has their own schemes in fighting for power.
Your Ice Well Bureau works single-mindedly,
relying on no faction.
If such a major event
as the assassination of the Emperor really happens,
all the blame
will be pushed onto you.
If there is any credit,
it will certainly not be yours.
It is a thankless task.
Do you understand?
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
I will keep it in mind.
Commander Chu, since you understand,
stop arresting innocent citizens of Dongjing indiscriminately.
Those who should be released,
release them all.
Farewell, Mr. Zhou.
Release them.
I ask you,
the Taoist who coerced you,
did he have a mole between his eyebrows?
My lord.
If you want to make a contribution,
he did.
And if not?
He didn't.
How dare you!
My lord,
that Taoist has the compound surname Situ.
In my judgment, he might be a Liangshan rebel.
Give me a chance to atone for my crimes.
I know their possible future moves.
Let me help you
catch the rebels.
Commander.
Lord Zhou's men
have returned.
They only asked
if we released the people.
I am
only passing a message.
It concerns His Majesty's safety.
If we don't catch the thieves,
no one is allowed to leave.
Take them away.
It's a bit tight.
Be gentle.
Old man,
you saved my life again.
I guessed
you weren't with those people.
If Lord Zhou wants to release them,
couldn't you find an excuse to send them away?
Do I have to teach you this?
Can't you even stall for an hour?
But Lord Zhou...
Whose side are you on?
Keep interrogating those people.
You're the one
who used the Fire Escape
to scare away Jackal Uncle.
Daughter.
How dare you!
No,
My Lord.
Forgive my presumption.
If it weren't for your skill in the Fire Escape,
you would be tortured by now.
You really look like my daughter.
Do you have a death wish?
No.
Tell the truth.
Who exactly are you,
and what is your relationship
with those people in the cave?
My name is Zhu Zitong.
In the past,
I roamed the martial world
and made a living as a street performer.
Because of my skill in the Fire Escape,
people in the martial world
call me Fire Sanlang.